<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>work on Curious Musings</title>
    <link>https://eludom.github.io/tags/work/</link>
    <description>Recent content in work on Curious Musings</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 00:00:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://eludom.github.io/tags/work/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Adding uncertainty in uncertain times</title>
      <link>https://eludom.github.io/posts/2020-06-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://eludom.github.io/posts/2020-06-30/</guid>
      <description>So, when life turns uncertain you have two choices. Cling to things that seem to add stability and certainty, i.e. try to &amp;ldquo;stay safe&amp;rdquo;, or embrace the uncertainty, live now, carpe diem, and do things would seem to be fulfilling now.
I&amp;rsquo;m choosing the latter. At 58, in the middle of a pandemic and social unrest, I&amp;rsquo;m moving to a startup. The following are notes from a friend who has been playing the silicon valley startup game for a few decades.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#34;​I&#39;m passionate about…&#34;​</title>
      <link>https://eludom.github.io/blog/im-passionate-about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://eludom.github.io/blog/im-passionate-about/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m passionate about&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; I&amp;rsquo;ve always hated that phrase. Because I thought it was fake. I thought it was trendy. I&amp;rsquo;ve reflexively reacted against trendy things for decades. Pet Rocks, Disco, TED talks, cryptocurrency&amp;hellip; But I am coming to see what the phrase is getting at. And I think I like it.
In a work world where human beings are called &amp;ldquo;resources&amp;rdquo;, where intelligent, creative, inquisitive, motivated people are subjected to management practices derived from 19th century steel mills and automotive assembly line production, the phrase &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m passionate about&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; is (can be) an attempt to re-assert humanity.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>